https://www.frostscience.org/privacy-policy/

This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 15, 2019
The Phillip and Patricia Frost Museum of Science (the “Company” or the “Museum”) is committed to your personal privacy and protecting the personal information that you provide to us or that we collect from you through your use of our website (including any and all additional, temporary, current and/or future websites, microsites and subdomains that include .frostscience.org, and related services, including without limitation, mobile websites, and mobile applications; all of the foregoing being hereinafter collectively referred to as the “Website”). This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected through the Website, including any related service, sales, marketing or event. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other third party website that may be accessible to or linked to from here. By visiting the Website, you agree to accept the practices described herein. The Company may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do make changes, we will post those changes here.
Notice to European Union (“EU”) Residents: This Privacy Policy and the policies contained herein are intended to comply with the “General Data Protection Regulation” (“GDPR”) and provide the appropriate protections with regard to the treatment of your information. If you have any questions about how we are processing your information, you may contact us at feedback@frostscience.org. If you believe we are unlawfully processing your personal information, you may contact your local data protection supervisory authority; to do so please visit ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm. For more information, see Section 10 below.
Table of Contents
1. Information we collect from you
a. General Information
b. Personal Information
2. How we use your information; who we share your information with
3. Cookies
4. How you can access your information
5. Security
6. Children’s privacy
7. External links
8. Visiting the Website from outside the United States
9. How to unsubscribe from email communications
10. Notice to EU Residents
11. Contact us
1. Information we collect from you.
a. General Information.  When you visit the Website, certain general information may be collected solely as a result of you navigating our Website.
This information may include IP addresses, browser information, which pages you visited, information collected through the use of “cookies” (see below), and similar, non-personal information.
We may collect and use information about your location based upon your IP address.
When you use a Company application or “app” on a mobile phone or tablet device, we will collect and use information about you in broadly the same way and for substantially similar purposes as when you use the Website. In addition, we may collect information about your location, via your privacy settings. You can change your privacy settings at any time, in order to turn off the functionality to share location information.
b. Personal Information.  Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) includes you name, email address, home/billing address, phone number, login information/password, and credit card number.
Instances in which PII may be collected include when you:
*Sign up for our newsletter or otherwise join our database
*Become a member of the Museum (or renew your membership)
*Make a gift or donation to the Museum
*Purchase tickets to the Museum or a Museum event online
*Place an online order with the Museum gift shop
*Participate in a marketing event (e.g. survey, sweepstakes)
*Post to the Museum’s online blog
*Create a user account
The decision to provide PII will always be yours; however, if you choose not to provide PII we may be unable to provide you with the service you requested.
2. How we use your information; who we share your information with
PII is collected to process donations and purchases, and to respond to requests for information. PII may be shared, on an as necessary basis, with third party agents and administrators who provide necessary services to the Museum.
We may also share PII with trusted business partners who we believe offer information or services which our users might be interested in.
In the event that PII is shared with such parties, we will always use appropriate measures to restrict such third parties from using your PII in any manner other than as necessary for the performance of their services and will make sure they protect your PII with appropriate measures of security.
Be advised, however, that we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties.
General (non PII) information may be used for a variety of purposes, and such information may be aggregated.
The Company reserves the right to disclose any information (including PII) in response to legal process, to establish or protect our legal rights, or as otherwise required by applicable law; if we believe such action is necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; if we believe such action is necessary to protect the legal rights of the Company, any Website user, or any other appropriate party; if we believe such action is necessary to protect the general public.
We may also disclose information (including PII) in the event of any change in legal status of the Company to a successor in interest or other relevant party.
3. Cookies
Cookies are small data text files that can be stored on your computer’s hard drive (if your Web browser permits). We use cookies to help us recognize your browser as a previous visitor and save and remember any preferences that may have been set while your browser was visiting the Website.
Cookies also help us customize the content and website experience provided to you on the Website. We also use cookies to help measure and research the effectiveness of Website features and e-mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon).
The “help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers should tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable most types of cookies. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to access many of the features offered on the Website.
The Website may also use web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs), which are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, that are placed in the code of a webpage. We may use web beacons to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one page of the Website sites to another, to deliver or communicate with cookies, and to improve site performance. We may also allow our service providers to use web beacons to help us understand which emails have been opened by recipients and to track the visitor traffic and other actions on our site.
4. How you can access your information
You can access and update your contact information by logging in to your account on the Website You can close your account by contacting us at the email address listed below. Please note that after you close an account, you will not be able to sign in or access any of your personal information. However, you can open a new account at any time. Please also note that we may retain certain information associated with your account in our archives, including for analytical purposes as well as for recordkeeping integrity.
5. Security
The Company uses industry-standard security protocols to protect the security of the PII (including financial information) that you provide to us.
While no website can guarantee 100% security, we take appropriate measures to protect the security of the information you provide to us. Only authorized individuals are permitted to access PII and may only access such information in connection with necessary business functions. We employ appropriate encryption technology to protect information when it is transmitted to the Website, and we use firewalls and other intrusion detection systems to prevent unauthorized access to information.
6. Children’s Privacy
The Website is intended for general audiences and is not generally directed to individuals who are under the age of 13.
The Company does not intentionally or knowingly collect PII from individuals under the age of 13.
If an individual under the age of 13 provides us with PII without parental consent, please contact us at feedback@frostscience.org to request removal of such information from the Company’s database.
7. External Links
The Website may contain links to other websites.
If you click on any of those links, you will leave the Website and will no longer be governed by this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing PII.
We cannot take responsibility for the content or information collection practices of linked websites.
8. Visiting the Website from outside the United States
If you are visiting the Website from outside the United States, you are advised that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States. The data protection and other laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and used as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
9. How to unsubscribe from receiving email or other electronic communications
You can opt-out of receiving email or other electronic communications by either (a) clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email or other electronic communication and follow the instructions to unsubscribe, or (b) send an email to feedback@frostscience.org asking to be unsubscribed.
10. Notice to EU Residents
EU residents have certain rights under the GDPR.
Among these rights are:
*Your right to access your personal information
*Your right to have your personal data deleted
*Your right to restrict how your personal data is processed
*Your right to withdraw you consent at any time.
You may contact us regarding these and other rights at feedback@frostscience.org.
11. Contact us
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please email us at feedback@frostscience.org or contact us at Patricia and Phillip Frost Museum of Science, 1101 Biscayne Blvd., Miami, FL 33132, Attention: Privacy Policy.
